[{"answer": " my friend!  my friend' roommate from college.. hello!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Saw it? I loved it! And thank you for the free tickets. You are so funny", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " There's a Costanza in that place?  Did he look like me? Did you talk to him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I gotta get that picture", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You know the Three Tenors", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " The other guy. ", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Oh, I put up my doll collection..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " What? What is it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What's going on in here?  Are you two still playing?! You've been up here three hours", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The first game?", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, that's dynamite", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who else is on the show", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who else is on the show", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " The Three Tenors?  Which one?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Uh.. It's not Poverotti.. It's not my friend.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Yeah, the other guy", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We call it.. the, uh.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The place to be! Yes! It's the place to be", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I know it's a joke. It's supposed to be a joke! Now I'm going on the my friend Show with nothing.  Nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I don't have any material", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " I can't make anything.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Follow through? What do you mean", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Hi my friend, it's my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hi my friend, it's my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Doll.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No, but he should be home soon", "qsentId": 26}]